I was sitting around,
just doing my thing,
When, all of a sudden,
I heard the bell ring.
I opened the door
and who should I meet . . .
"Hi, I'm Zac,
I just moved to your street."
He asked for an egg,
in a nice polite way.
"Sure," I replied. "I just bought some today."
So I gave him an egg
and he laughed with delight.
And so he ran off
and was out of my sight.
Zac returned moments later
—said "how do you do?"
He asked for some eggs—
but now he wants . . . two.
I gave him two eggs, and he
soon skipped away.
(I hope it's the last time
I'll see him today.)
A little while later
he's back ringing the bell.
What was he up to?
I just couldn't tell.
Again it was Zac,
won't he just let me be?
Now I'm giving him eggs—
this time he wants . . . three!
So I turned off the doorbell!
A few minutes later—
a knock at the door.
Zac says "I'm sorry",
but now he wants . . . four!
So I gave him four eggs,
'cause I'm nice that way.
And he looked very happy,
and just went away.
The rest of the day
I just sat in my chair.
I kept checking the door,
but he wasn't there.
And in all of that time
he didn't come back.
I realized I missed him—
my new friend, Zac.
At the end of the day,
when the sun had just set.
I still hadn't seen him;
I was kinda upset.
I decided to check—
give it one last try . . .
And there he stood, with . . .
. . . a lemon meringue pie!
I brought him inside
for a warm cup of tea,
And we talked and we talked—
just Zac and me.
He spoke of God's love and
His grace that was free,
And how Jesus died for
lost people like me.
Now I felt very glad for the
things that Zac said,
And I thought of God's love
as I headed to bed.
But one thing still bugged me,
I haven't a clue.
With all of those eggs,
just what did he do?
I thought and I thought,
then I understood why—
You need lots of eggs for . . .
. . . a lemon meringue pie!
But there's so much pie left!
We thought,
"What should we do?"
So we came round this morning
to share it with you!